{
    "id": "543aee105c304cf3b2d439d4d170fe36",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is …………………….. woman in her village.",
            "description": "The superlative is used to compare one person or thing with the whole group to which they belong. ",
            "answers": [
                "the richer",
                "the richest",
                "the rich"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bbee683ccfc7466fb25a562bd53e0a2b"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ……………………….. birthday gift I have ever received.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the goodest",
                "best",
                "the best"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "004e19bf5a2348cfa8d7091aae14a9aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t drink as ………………………… as you do.",
            "description": "Many indicates number much indicates quantity. ",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9a319152ef24d78b143070f37f1388c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tom is …………………………. of my four children.",
            "description": "Youngest is the superlative form.",
            "answers": [
                "younger",
                "the youngest",
                "the most youngest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c8f1a31a8b81475c90560ccb2e7202bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Haven’t you paid the fees ……………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "still",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d69ecd8c5d984e2caea175c3593360aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "They …………………………. ever go out.",
            "description": "Hardly ever means the same as almost never.",
            "answers": [
                "hardly",
                "almost",
                "nearly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "905079c3ec80461488dd357a19b461df"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………………. late for work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "never",
                "ever",
                "hardly ever"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eaba92a5f2654103b359e66bfc4182ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have not ……………………….. heard from them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "already",
                "still"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "63dbb2a37b444df9b3d1e58b27e2a25e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She can speak French ……………………….. fluently.",
            "description": "Quite indicates a higher degree of something. ",
            "answers": [
                "Quite",
                "Quiet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f7c9253b7da24499be026bf4cbf0e2a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………….. than I thought.",
            "description": "Cleverer is the comparative form of clever. ",
            "answers": [
                "clever",
                "more clever",
                "cleverer"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ce2a047dc17a4e5cafd5222f7256b6a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ate ………………………… anything.",
            "description": "Hardly anything means almost nothing. ",
            "answers": [
                "hardly",
                "almost",
                "rarely"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "00c7e67fc9114c35a91e562461a5eee0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She said ……………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nothing",
                "anything"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b91d31b540dc4f17a242023eec81a3f2"
        }
    ]
}